For more than 2000 years ...
... humanity was stuck in the footsteps of it's ancestors ...
... trying to keep our world in reach of our tiny minds.
We called a fraction of a portion of space our holy nation to defend from all intruders.
Stuck in this loop of simplicity it took some time until the creators amongst us surpassed their counters ...
... we became wonders amongst the stars.
Leaving for new, distant frontiers.
And in a sea of redish dust ... we found a fountain of life ...
"Commander? What do I do?"
The intimations of a future in a life bursting universe and it's composition of infinity freed us from our human constraints.
We found water on Mars.
So we did what any self-respecting civilization would ...
... make beer!
Beer from Mars