Will Weekly - Talk + Draw
What's going on YouTube!? This is Will. Welcome to Will Weekly! This is Talk + Draw Episode 7.
Today I'll be doing a comic I came across about 5 months ago on random websites.
The author's name is David Revoy and the comic is called Pepper and Carrot.
It's a very well drawn, well written comic. I mean the stories... I think they're on Episode 10 and Episode 11 should be coming out shortly ...
They're very short comic books. Maybe about 8 or 10 panels. But they're very cute, very whimsical and very funny.
The two characters are very original. The artist takes you away to a whole other world with his drawings.
The style of his fantasy drawing is ... to me ... is remeniscent of the old school RPGs I used to play on Playstation ...
... like Suikoden or Chrono Cross or Final Fantasy 9 especially.
Actually the main character Pepper, she reminds me of a female version of Vivi.
Just a which or a mage ... but she has her own quirky little personality and after you read a few comics you'll grow to love her love the artistry of it as well.
and he's a very humble dude. He gives basic tutorials on how he does his craft ...
gives advice on the industry ... he writes out step by step how he made all his comics ...
... and it's actually really cool to read because he's utilizing Open Source and "permissive", 100% free and forever.
He puts his stuff online for free, absolutely. And he uses Open Source Software ...
... and I think the main software that he uses is called Krita (krita.org) ...
... and it's not as popular as Photoshop's, etc but I've actually played with Krita and I love the concept of it!
It's a very simplistic interface and is very good for artists as far as doing flats and line arts.
And as you'll see on this video the way I do my line art can be kinda cumbersome depending on the type of art I'm doing.
The demo that I saw that he actually gave a tutorial for Krita was absolutely wonderful ...
... to the point where I reached out to the company and said when are you guys gonna have the Mac version ...
... because the one particular thing that I wanted to use has a bug with it on the Mac version of the software.
So they're still gonna work in that as they get a little more popular and I can't wait to have it because it will speed up my flatting process probably 3x at the least.
But yea, like I was saying, his name is David Revoy. These are his two characters. They are by no means any of my characters that I own.
This is me as a fan. I am going to tweet this to him and post it on his facebook to make sure he understands that I did it because he does accept fan art.
And this is just me paying homage to the characters and the creativity and the ability to take two unknown characters ...
... and after a few episodes of reading, you're entirely thrust into their world and you understand different individuals that encompass this world ...
... as well as get to know the characters on that much more of a deep level.
I think that's a very impressive thing for an artist to be able to pull off in such a short period of time.
So I commend him 100% and I am 100% a fan of him.
This is the type of thing I hope to do with my personal IPs is to just create a character that takes you away that takes you away to an entirely world ...
... transport you and make you fall in love with them and make you want to see what their next adventures are.
See what they're up to and hopefully we can all be on the same page as artists and fans of art ... where we can have ...
... because the Internet is very key to this lifestyle because it's a very Open Source world now ...
... where you don't have to go the comic shop every week to get the newest comic. This is all on line.
So if we can have the same thought process that David Revoy has as far as having everything Open Source ...
... and using the "honor system" with pay ... because yes, artists, you do need to get paid ...
... but he's managed to capivate a nice fan base and they take care of him ...
... and I think it's a wonder thing and I'm definitely one of his fans and will be for the forseeable future.
So I just wanted to let you guys know. Thanks for watching! Hope you enjoyed the video.
Please subscribe if you did. Talk to you guys later!